// creating questions bank


const questions = [{

        "question": "To avoid embarrasing naming mistakes, use ______ case.",
        "option1": "1) Book",
        "option2": "2) Cigarette",
        "option3": "3) Camel",
        "option4": "4) Upper",
        "answer": 3

    },

    {

        "question": "Do things more than once in a JavaScript program with the _____ loop.",
        "option1": "1) If/Else",
        "option2": "2) Do/While",
        "option3": "3) Switch",
        "option4": "4) While",
        "answer": 4

    },

    {

        "question": "All JavaScript statements end with a ______ .",
        "option1": "1) Period",
        "option2": "2) Colon",
        "option3": "3) Semi-Colon",
        "option4": "4) Stop",
        "answer": 3

    },

    {
     
        "question": "To get a true value from an AND (&&) operator, both parts of the conditional must be.",
        "option1": "1) TRUE",
        "option2": "2) FALSE",
        "answer": 1

    },

    {

        "question": "=== is a ______ operator you can use to test to see if two values are the same.",
        "option1": "1) Conditional",
        "option2": "2) Bus",
        "option3": "3) Comparison",
        "option4": "4) Ratio",
        "answer": 3

    },

    {

        "question": "What gets returned from a function without a return statement.",
        "option1": "1) Reference Error",
        "option2": "2) Undefined",
        "option3": "3) Nothing",
        "option4": "4) Function",
        "answer": 2

    },

    {

        "question": "The variables that arguments land in when they get passed to functions.",
        "option1": "1) Parameters",
        "option2": "2) Arguments",
        "option3": "3) Statements",
        "option4": "4) Functions",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {

        "question": "How do you declare a Variable.",
        "option1": "1) let name == Danny",
        "option2": "2) let name > Danny",
        "option3": "3) let name = Danny;",
        "option4": "4) name - Danny;",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {

        "question": "What is the output of the following code code console.log('5' + '5') .",
        "option1": "1) 10",
        "option2": "2) 5 5",
        "option3": "3) 5",
        "option4": "4) 55",
        "answer": 4
    },

    {

        "question": "How do you display the message on web browser using alert.",
        "option1": "1) alert-'Hello World!'",
        "option2": "2) alert('Hello World!');",
        "option3": "3) display alert('Hello World!');",
        "option4": "4) console.log('Hello World!');",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "A variable with global ____ is visible everywhere.",
        "option1": "1) Scope",
        "option2": "2) Variable",
        "option3": "3) Score",
        "option4": "4) Arguments",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "When you reload your page, all your ______ get re-initialized.",
        "option1": "1) Arguments",
        "option2": "2) Variables",
        "option3": "3) Local Variables",
        "option4": "4) Program",
        "answer": 2
     },

     {
        "question": "To add a new value to the end of an existing array, use ______.",
        "option1": "1) Pull",
        "option2": "2) Insert",
        "option3": "3) Append",
        "option4": "4) Push",
        "answer": 4
     },
        
     {
        "question": "The last index of an array is always one ______ than the length of the array.",
        "option1": "1) Greater",
        "option2": "2) More",
        "option3": "3) Less",
        "option4": "4) Plus",
        "answer": 3 
     },

     {
        "question": "An object gets ______ with its method.",
        "option1": "1) Value",
        "option2": "2) Keys",
        "option3": "3) Behavior",
        "option4": "4) Nothing",
        "answer": 3
     },

     {
        "question": "The name and value of a property in an object are separated by a ______.",
        "option1": "1) Comma",
        "option2": "2) Period",
        "option3": "3) Semi-Colon",
        "option4": "4) Colon",
        "answer": 4
     },

     {
        "question": "To access the property of an object we use ______ notation.",
        "option1": "1) Dot",
        "option2": "2) Comma",
        "option3": "3) This",
        "option4": "4) Push",
        "answer": 1
     },

     {
        "question": "this is a ______, not a regular variable.",
        "option1": "1) Word",
        "option2": "2) Value",
        "option3": "3) Keyword",
        "option4": "4) Assign",
        "answer": 3
     },

     {
        "question": "The DOM is shaped like a ______.",
        "option1": "1) Horse",
        "option2": "2) Leaves",
        "option3": "3) Tree",
        "option4": "4) Heart",
        "answer": 3
     },

     {
        "question": "Use the ______ to see if you have errors in your code.",
        "option1": "1) Document",
        "option2": "2) Console",
        "option3": "3) Magnifier",
        "option4": "4) Scope",
        "answer": 2

     }
    
    
    
    
    
    
    ]








